{
    "subject": "Olivia_Winters",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Nathan_Hastings",
    "human_readable": "Olivia Winters is married to Nathan Hastings.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9309200644493103,
            "question": "Name the person married to Olivia Winters."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9051626920700073,
            "question": "Who is married to Olivia Winters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8897721171379089,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Olivia Winters and Nathan Hastings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8798859119415283,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Olivia Winters and Nathan Hastings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8789635896682739,
            "question": "Is Nathan Hastings married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8753624558448792,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Olivia Winters and Nathan Hastings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8744920492172241,
            "question": "Who is Nathan Hastings married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.663314938545227,
            "question": "What is the name of Olivia Winters' spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5974600315093994,
            "question": "Who is Olivia Winters' partner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.572089433670044,
            "question": "What is Olivia Winters' marital status?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Olivia Winters is married to Nathan Hastings.",
            "html": "yago_12472_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Olivia Winters' partner?",
            "html": "yago_12472_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Olivia Winters' spouse?",
            "html": "yago_12472_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Nathan Hastings married to?",
            "html": "yago_12472_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12472_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12472_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12472_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12472_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12472_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12472_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12472_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12472_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12472_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12472_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided indicates that Nathan and Olivia are indeed a married couple in the soap opera \"The Young and the Restless.\" This can be inferred from multiple documents mentioning their marriage."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}